Guide to the Freedom to Marry Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Program Files, 1973-2016; Series IV; 45.84; 113 boxes
  - Campaign files, 1990-2015
    - National campaign files, 1990-2015
      - Freedom to Marry Week
        - Kit (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - General information (Box 102, Folder 3)
      - Gill action 2009 campaign briefing binder (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - Lambda legal defense and education fund petitions, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - "Left alone" a Freedom to Marry short, 1 (Box 86)
      - Lopez, Sergio notebooks, 2014 (Box 102, Folder 5-6)
      - Marriage Resolutions 2001
        - 2007 (Box 57, Folder 6)
        - Activists: contacts, 2001 (Box 102, Folder 7)
        - Gay elected official, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 7)
        - Alaska, 2001 (Box 57, Folder 8)
        - Alaska: individuals: general, 2009 (Box 57, Folder 9)
        - Arizona (Box 57, Folder 10)
        - Arizona: Individuals: general, 1998 (Box 102, Folder 8)
        - Arizona: organizations (Box 102, Folder 9)
        - California (Box 57, Folder 11-12)
        - California: California state bar, 1997 (Box 102, Folder 10)
        - California: individuals: community leaders, 1997 (Box 102, Folder 11)
        - California: individuals: faith groups + individuals, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 12)
        - California: individuals: general, 2000 (Box 102, Folder 13)
        - California: organizations, 1995-2000 (Box 102, Folder 14)
        - Colorado (Box 57, Folder 13)
        - Colorado: individuals: general, 1999-2001 (Box 102, Folder 15)
        - Colorado: organizations, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 16)
        - Congregations, 2003 (Box 158, Folder 14)
        - Connecticut (Box 57, Folder 14)
        - Connecticut: individuals: general, 1996-2001 (Box 102, Folder 17)
        - Connecticut: organizations, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 18)
        - Database, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 1)
        - DB [Database] (MARR)+ Rolodex (EW) (Box 57, Folder 15)
        - DC: individuals: faith groups & individuals, 1995 (Box 103, Folder 2)
        - DC: individuals: general (Box 103, Folder 3)
        - DC: organizations, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 4)
        - Delaware: individuals: faith groups and individuals (Box 103, Folder 5)
        - Delaware: organizations, 1995 (Box 103, Folder 6)
        - Endorsement lists (Box 103, Folder 7)
        - Faith groups and individuals, 1995 (Box 103, Folder 8)
        - Florida (Box 57, Folder 16)
        - Florida: individuals: general, 2000-2001 (Box 103, Folder 9)
        - Florida: organizations, 1995-2001 (Box 103, Folder 10)
        - Florida (Box 103, Folder 11)
        - Georgia (Box 57, Folder 17)
        - Georgia: individuals: general, 1995-1999 (Box 103, Folder 12)
        - General (Box 103, Folder 13-15)
        - General (Box 104, Folder 1-2)
        - Georgia: Emory University, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 18)
        - Hawaii, 1997-1999 (Box 104, Folder 3)
        - Illinois (Box 58, Folder 1)
        - Illinois: individuals: faith groups and individuals, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 4)
        - Illinois: organizations, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 5)
        - Indiana (Box 58, Folder 2)
        - Individuals, 1995-1998 (Box 104, Folder 6)
        - Iowa (Box 58, Folder 3)
        - Kansas, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 4)
        - Kansas: Individuals: general (Box 58, Folder 5)
        - Kansas: organizations (Box 58, Folder 6)
        - Kentucky (Box 58, Folder 7)
        - Kentucky: individuals: faith groups and individuals, 2001 (Box 104, Folder 7)
        - Kentucky: individual: general (Box 104, Folder 8)
        - Louisiana: organizations (Box 104, Folder 9)
        - Lists of signers, 2003 (Box 104, Folder 10)
        - Individuals, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 11)
        - Massachusetts, 2004 (Box 58, Folder 8)
        - Massachusetts: individuals: faith groups and individuals, 1996-2001 (Box 104, Folder 12)
        - Massachusetts: organizations, 1995-2004 (Box 104, Folder 13)
        - Massachusetts, 1999-2000 (Box 58, Folder 9)
        - MCC, 1995-2004 (Box 104, Folder 14)
        - Maryland, 2001-2002 (Box 58, Folder 10)
        - Maryland: individuals: general, 1996-1999 (Box 104, Folder 15)
        - Maryland: organizations (Box 104, Folder 16)
        - Maine: organizations (Box 104, Folder 17)
        - Michigan (Box 58, Folder 11)
        - Michigan: individuals: general, 1999-2004 (Box 104, Folder 18)
        - Minnesota (Box 58, Folder 12)
        - Minnesota: individuals: community leaders (Box 104, Folder 19)
        - Minnesota: individuals: faith groups and individuals (Box 104, Folder 20)
        - Minnesota: individuals: general, 2001 (Box 104, Folder 21)
        - Minnesota: organizations (Box 104, Folder 22)
        - Missouri (Box 58, Folder 13)
        - Missouri: individuals: general, 1999-2001 (Box 104, Folder 23)
        - Missouri: organizations (Box 104, Folder 24)
        - Mister Select signatory backup for activists (Box 58, Folder 14)
        - Mississippi: organizations (Box 104, Folder 25)
        - Montana: individuals: general (Box 104, Folder 26)
        - Montana: organizations (Box 104, Folder 27)
        - North Carolina: individuals: general, 1996-2002 (Box 104, Folder 28)
        - North Carolina: organizations (Box 104, Folder 29)
        - Nebraska: individuals: general (Box 105, Folder 1)
        - Nebraska: organizations (Box 105, Folder 2)
        - New Hampshire: organizations, 2001 (Box 158, Folder 15)
        - New Jersey: general, 2002 (Box 105, Folder 3)
        - New York law school (Box 105, Folder 4)
        - New York (entered), 2002 (Box 105, Folder 5)
        - New York: general, 1998-2001 (Box 105, Folder 6)
        - New York: individuals: community leaders, 2004 (Box 105, Folder 7)
        - New York: individuals: faith groups and individuals, 2001-2003 (Box 105, Folder 8)
        - New York: organizations, 2003 (Box 105, Folder 9)
        - New Mexico: individuals: general, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 10)
        - Nevada (Box 58, Folder 15)
        - Nevada: individuals: general, 1996-1999 (Box 105, Folder 11)
        - Nevada: organization (Box 105, Folder 12)
        - Ohio, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 16)
        - Ohio: individuals: general, 1995-1999 (Box 105, Folder 13)
        - Ohio: organizations (Box 105, Folder 14)
        - Oklahoma: individuals: faith groups and individuals (Box 105, Folder 15)
        - Oklahoma: individuals: general, 2001-2003 (Box 105, Folder 16)
        - Oklahoma: organizations (Box 105, Folder 17)
        - Oregon: individuals: general, 1998-2000 (Box 105, Folder 18)
        - Oregon: organizations, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 19)
        - Organizations, 1994-2001 (Box 106, Folder 1)
        - Pennsylvania (Box 58, Folder 17)
        - Pennsylvania: individuals: faith groups and individuals, 1995 (Box 106, Folder 2)
        - Pennsylvania: First Unitarian Church, 2006 (Box 59, Folder 1)
        - Pennsylvania: individuals: general, 1994-2001 (Box 106, Folder 3)
        - Pennsylvania: organizations (Box 106, Folder 4)
        - Pending, 2002-2004 (Box 58, Folder 18)
        - Puerto Rico, 2001 (Box 59, Folder 2)
        - Rhode Island, 2001 (Box 59, Folder 3)
        - Rhode Island: organizations (Box 106, Folder 5)
        - South Carolina (Box 59, Folder 4)
        - South Carolina: individuals: faith groups and individuals, 1996-1997 (Box 106, Folder 6)
        - South Carolina: individuals: general, 2000 (Box 106, Folder 7)
        - Tennessee, 1999-2001 (Box 59, Folder 5)
        - Tennessee: individuals: general, 1995-2000 (Box 106, Folder 8)
        - Tennessee: individuals: faith groups and individuals, 1995 (Box 158, Folder 16)
        - Tennessee: organizations, 1995 (Box 106, Folder 9)
        - Texas, 2000-2002 (Box 59, Folder 6)
        - Texas: individuals: community leaders, 1995-2003 (Box 106, Folder 10)
        - Texas: individuals: faith groups and individuals (Box 106, Folder 11)
        - Texas: individuals: general, 1995-2003 (Box 106, Folder 12)
        - Texas: organizations, 1995 (Box 106, Folder 13)
        - Texas: Rice University (Box 106, Folder 14)
        - Utah: Weber State University (Box 106, Folder 15)
        - Virginia (Box 59, Folder 10)
        - Virginia: individuals: faith groups and individuals, 1996 (Box 106, Folder 16)
        - Virginia: individuals: general, 1995-2004 (Box 106, Folder 17)
        - Virginia: organizations (Box 106, Folder 18)
        - Virginia: Randolph Macon Women's College, 2001 (Box 106, Folder 19)
        - Washington, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 7)
        - Washington: individuals: general, 1995-2004 (Box 106, Folder 21)
        - Washington: organizations, 1996-1999 (Box 106, Folder 22)
        - Washington: individuals: faith groups and individuals (Box 106, Folder 20)
        - Wisconsin (Box 59, Folder 8)
        - Wisconsin: individuals: general, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 23)
        - Wisconsin: organizations, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 24)
        - West Virginia (Box 59, Folder 9)
        - West Virginia: individuals: general, 2000 (Box 106, Folder 25)
      - Marriage resolutions: Arizona: Act out at Arizona State University/LGBTQ coalition, 2002-2004 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Marriage resolution celebrity signatories, 1990-1999 (Box 59, Folder 12-14)
      - Marriage resolution documents, 2007 (Box 59, Folder 15)
      - Marriage resolution documents, 2007 (Box 60, Folder 1-4)
      - Marriage resolutions: Illinois: Unitarian Church, 2002-2004 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Marriage resolutions: New York (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Marriage resolutions Pennsylvania (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Marriage resolutions: Pennsylvania: Undergraduate student government, 2001-2002 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Marriage resolutions: Vermont: Individuals: General (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Moving marriage forward presentation (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Marriage resolutions (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Meeting notes (Box 131, Folder 1-2)
      - Messaging that works presentation and luncheon event briefing, 2012 May 2 (Box 106, Folder 26)
      - New Jersey marriage endorsements
        - Attorneys, 2001-2002 (Box 61, Folder 8)
        - Businesses, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 9)
        - Community leaders, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 10)
        - Educators, 2002 (Box 61, Folder 11)
        - General individuals, 2001-2002 (Box 61, Folder 12-13)
        - Healthcare endorsements, 2001-2002 (Box 61, Folder 14)
        - Organizations, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - Photo release form (Box 106, Folder 27)
      - Resolutions to file (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Resource guides (Box 62, Folder 2-3)
      - Senior web producer (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Spanish radio tour, 2006 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Student marriage resolution, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Thomas J. Bradley v. Empire Blue Cross/Blue Shield, 1990 July (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - Website general, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Wash pac complaint (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - "Why marriage" brochure - Spanish, circa 2002 (Box 106, Folder 28)
      - Work files (Box 106, Folder 29)
      - 2003 end-of-the-year report (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - State campaign files, 1992-2007
      - California
        - 2005-2006 (Box 106, Folder 30)
        - California equity project, 2006 (Box 107, Folder 1)
        - "Let California Ring", 2006-2008; 7 (Box 107, Folder 2-6, Box 138, Box 139, Box 140, Box 141, Box 142, Box 143, Box 144, Box 145)
          - The Grover Park group, 2016-M-0049-0007; 1 (Box 138)
          - Zimmerman & Markman inc: political consulting and advertising demo reel, 2016-M-0049-0008; 1 (Box 139)
          - AGM demo reel, 2016-M-0049-0009; 1 (Box 140)
          - Creative reel: The equality project RFP Messaging and Media Consultant, 2016-M-0049-0010; 1 (Box 141)
          - Interactive samples: The Equality project RFP messaging and media consultant, 2016-M-0049-0011; 1 (Box 142)
          - Agency video: DDB seattle, 2016-M-0049-0012; 1 (Box 143)
          - Case study video: DDB Seattle, 2016-M-0049-0013; 1 (Box 144)
          - www.publicinterest.tv, 2016-M-0049-0014; 1 (Box 145)
        - Knight Initiative material, 1999-2000 (Box 107, Folder 8)
        - Knight Initiative material, 1999-2000 (Box 108, Folder 1-2)
        - Lambda legal, 1999-2006 (Box 108, Folder 3)
        - MECA, 2001 (Box 108, Folder 4)
      - Connecticut, 2005-2006; 1 (Box 108, Folder 5, Box 146)
        - Connecticut Women's Hall of Fame 2006 inductees: Helen Keller, Mary Townsend Seymour, Anne Stanback "Bread and Roses 2006", 2016-M-0049-0015; 1 (Box 146)
      - Hawaii Marriage Case supreme court 1992 argument, 1 (Box 87)
      - Illinois, 2006 (Box 108, Folder 6)
      - Iowa, 2005-2006 (Box 108, Folder 7)
      - Maine, 2005-2006 (Box 108, Folder 8)
      - Marriage equality for same-sex couples: A Connecticut Conversation, 1 (Box 88)
      - Maryland, 2005-2006 (Box 108, Folder 9)
      - Massachusetts testimony book, 2002-2003 (Box 108, Folder 10-11)
      - New Hampshire, 2005-2006 (Box 108, Folder 12)
      - New Jersey, 2005-2006 (Box 108, Folder 13)
      - New Jersey petitions (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - New York, 2005-2006 (Box 109, Folder 1)
      - Oregon, 2006 (Box 109, Folder 2)
      - Oregon campaign "No on 36" poster (Box 80)
      - Other states, 2006 (Box 109, Folder 3)
      - Rhode Island, 2005-2006 (Box 109, Folder 3)
      - Vermont, 2006 (Box 109, Folder 4)
      - Washington, 2005-2007 (Box 109, Folder 5)
      - West Virginia, 2003 (Box 109, Folder 6)
      - Wisconsin, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1996-2010
    - Marriage related notes and news clippings, 1996-1998 (Box 67, Folder 6-8)
    - 2004-2010 (Box 63, Folder 1-7)
    - 2004-2010 (Box 64, Folder 1-6)
    - 2004-2010 (Box 65, Folder 1-7)
    - 2004-2010 (Box 66, Folder 1-6)
    - 2004-2010 (Box 67, Folder 1-2)
    - The Gay & Lesbian review, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - The effects of marriage (article), 2006 July (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Magazines, 2009 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Polling files, 1988-2010
    - 1988-2001 (Box 109, Folder 11-13)
    - Interracial marriage, 2001 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - 2002 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - 2003 (Box 110, Folder 1-3)
    - American civil liberties union, Beldon Russonello messaging, 2003 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - 2004 (Box 110, Folder 4-6)
    - 2004 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - 2005 (Box 111, Folder 2-3)
    - 2007 (Box 112, Folder 1-2)
    - 2008 (Box 112, Folder 3-5)
    - 2009 (Box 112B, Folder 1-3)
    - 2009-2010 (Box 112B, Folder 4)
  - Communication files, 1991-2010
    - Annual report, 2004 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Annual report attachments, 2004 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Ashay Communications, 2005 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Ashay media group, 2005-2006 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Ashay color proofs, 2005 (Box 113, Folder 2-3)
    - At the crossroads: African American attitudes, perception and beliefs towards marriage equality (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Baltimore case, 2006 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Beyond marriage, 2006 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Bibliography on Freedom to Marry, 2001 June 1 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Bizvox, 2003-2006 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Black prides, 2005 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Blog ads, 2007 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Book - Patron Saint productions (web marketing), 2005 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Book promotion/publicist search, 2005 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Budget, 2005 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Budget, 2005-2006 (Box 158, Folder 16)
    - Business partners: love & pride, 2005 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - California - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 2005-2006 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Calendar campaigns, 2007 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - California, 2007 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - California Conference National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 2006 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - California Why Marriage (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Campaigns/partnerships/declined, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Caplan communications, 2005-2006 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Caregiving: the task force, 2004 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Children of Lesbians and Gays everywhere (colage), 2006 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Civil marriage collaborative 2004 meeting binder (Box 114, Folder 9-10)
    - Civil marriage collaborative, 2004-2006 (Box 114, Folder 11-12)
    - Civil marriage collaborative, committee meeting, 2004 July (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Civil collaborative, committee meeting, 2004 July (Box 115, Folder 1-2)
    - Coalition partners, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Colage radio tour: Children of Lesbians and Gays Everywhere, 2006 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Communications associate search, 2005-2006 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Connecticut Love Makes a Family, 2001 May 3 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Couples Eric Marcoux and Eugene Woodward, 2003 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Courting equality, a documentary of America's first legal same-sex marriage (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - CQ researcher gay marriage, 2003 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - CQ weekly, 2006 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Creating change, 2004 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Creating change, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Creating change, 2006 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Creating change: transparencies (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Cross sponsorships, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Communications department - admin, 2005 May 24 (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Department budget (Box 158, Folder 17)
    - Department of communication
      - Communications strategy, 2005 (Box 158, Folder 18)
      - Communication team to-do list, 2006 May (Box 158, Folder 19)
      - Monthly report, 2003-2005 (Box 158, Folder 20)
      - Subscriptions (Box 158, Folder 21)
      - Workplan, 2005-2006 (Box 158, Folder 22-25)
      - Workplan documents, 2006 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Director's meeting, 2006 August 16 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Directory of lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender services and resources, 2001 June (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - E update (Box 115, Folder 17-18)
    - Evan Wolfson article website printout, 2010 October 21 (Box 115, Folder 19)
    - Evan Wolfson book reviews, 2004 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Evan Wolfson permission to print, 2008 November (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Events (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Family law quarterly, 2006 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Fenton placements, 2004 April (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Files of Samiya Bashir
      - Burrelle's Luce, 2004 (Box 116, Folder 4-5)
      - June third, 2007 (Box 159, Folder 3)
      - Media lists (Box 159, Folder 4-5)
      - Department of communication work plan, 2005-2006 (Box 159, Folder 6)
      - We are family, 2005 (Box 116, Folder 6)
      - Wed Rock, 2005 (Box 159, Folder 7-8)
      - WIMN's voices, 2006 (Box 159, Folder 9)
      - Winter/research resumes (Box 116, Folder 7-8)
      - Writer/research resumes (Box 117, Folder 1-2)
    - FMA 20/20 vision (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Freedom to Marry day/historical, 1999-2004 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Freedom photo (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - For Richer, For Poorer (FR/FP), 2007 (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - General: 2005 files
      - Advertisements, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - The Blogosphere, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Films/videos, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Iowa marriage talking points coalition partners, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Lambda taking points New York decisions, 2006 July 6 (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Non-gay wedding website (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - Online websites (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - Press lists (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Press releases (Box 68, Folder 15-16)
      - Print material email blasts (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - Print materials general, 2004 (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - Print materials partner samples (Box 68, Folder 19)
      - Public interest television (Box 68, Folder 20)
      - Red carpet - freedom photos (Box 68, Folder 21)
      - Religious endorsements website (Box 68, Folder 22)
      - Talking Points (Box 68, Folder 23)
      - Talking Points Federal Marriage Amendment (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Talking points Freedom to Marry New York State Decision, 2006 July 6 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Washington State/Marriage (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Website bids (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Gill foundation (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Healthy living conference, 2005 (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - Hispanic communications network (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Human rights, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - I do but I can't: The impact of marriage denial on the mental health and sexual citizenship of lesbians and gay men in the United States, 2006 March (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Issues interaction (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Landscape, 2006 (Box 159, Folder 13)
    - Latino radio tour, 2006 (Box 159, Folder 14)
    - Leasbians are women too, 2006 (Box 159, Folder 15)
    - Lewis & Winslow vs. Harris, 2006 (Box 159, Folder 16)
    - LGBT [Lesbian, gay, bisexual, trans*] career survey report, 2008 November (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - LGBTQI [Lesbian, gay, bisexual, trans*, queer, intersex] press, 2005 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Lisbeth: pending issues and notes (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Lisbeth pending issues: 2005 annual report (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Love makes a family (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Loving anniversary, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Mario Cuomo: 20/20 vision, 2006 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Marriage equality and lessons for the scary work of winning pamphlet (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Marriage equality in reach (Evan) (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Marriage equality matters, 2006 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Marriage in African American communities, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Marriage matters ad, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Marriage matters ad authorization, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Marriage victory plan New York State (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Marriage 101 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - MCM notes, 2006 December 11 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Media trained couples by market (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Meeting and program notes (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - MEM conference call, 2006 (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Meeting notes, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Megan Kinninger (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Michael Wolfson/AOL (Box 118, Folder 10-11)
    - Monday marriage message, 2007 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Monteiro & co (book publicity), 2005 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Musgrave amendment, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 2005 June 10 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - National Association of Black Journalists (NABJ), 2005-2006 (Box 118, Folder 16-17)
    - National Black Justice coalition, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - National Latina LGBT working committee, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - National Latino/a coalition for justice, 2005 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - NBJC: National Black Justice Coalition summit, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 20)
    - New Hampshire freedom to marry coalition (Box 118, Folder 21)
    - New Jersey decision, 2006 October 25 (Box 118, Folder 22)
    - New York State black gay network, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 23)
    - New York State court of appeals decision, 2006 July 6 (Box 118, Folder 24)
    - New Jersey decision preparation, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 25)
    - National Lesbian and Gay Law Association (NLGLA) (Box 118, Folder 26-27)
    - National Lesbian and Gay Law Association (NLGLA) (Box 119, Folder 1-2)
    - Officer affliliation (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Op-eds, 2010 October 22 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Page one news media invoice and proposal (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Partners events, 2005 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Partners NOW, 2005 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Partners pieces, 2005 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Partnerships: love and pride, 2005 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Photo contest winner, 2007 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Positive collaboration meeting LA (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Press releases communications, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Program case for marriage, 2004 (Box 119, Folder 15)